A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.1, Series 100 International - Series 257 Virgin Islands, U.S.A. FA386a
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Illinois, 1924-1959; 216; 11 Cubic Feet; 27 __Boxes __11 cubic feet
  - Illinois - Social Sciences, 216.S
    - University of Chicago - Community Research, 1931-1941 (Box 20, Folder 282)
    - University of Chicago - Community Research, 1931-1941 (Box 20, Folder 283)
    - University of Chicago - Community Research, 1942-1945 (Box 21, Folder 284)
    - University of Chicago - Community Research - Report, 1930 (Box 21, Folder 285)
    - University of Chicago - Fiscal Policy, 1948-1951 (Box 21, Folder 286)
    - University of Chicago - Industrial Relations, 1944-1951 (Box 21, Folder 287)
    - University of Chicago - Industrial Relations, 1944-1951 (Box 21, Folder 288)
    - University of Chicago - Industrial Relations - Reports, 1944-1951; 5 Items (Box 21, Folder 289)
    - University of Chicago - Industrial Relations - Reprints, 1947; 2 Items (Box 21, Folder 290)
    - University of Chicago - Industrialism, 1940-1952 (Box 21, Folder 291)
    - University of Chicago - Industrialism, 1940-1952 (Box 21, Folder 292)
    - University of Chicago - Machotha, Otakar - (Refugee, Travel, Sociology), 1948 (Box 21, Folder 293)
    - University of Chicago - Millis, Harry - (Labor Legislation Study), 1947-1950 (Box 21, Folder 294)
    - University of Chicago - Morrison, J. A. - (Travel, Soviet Regional Administration), 1937-1940 (Box 21, Folder 295)
    - University of Chicago - Morrison, J. A. - (Travel, Soviet Regional Administration) - Pamphlet, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 296)
    - University of Chicago - Public Administration, 1931-1939 (Box 21, Folder 297)
    - University of Chicago - Public Administration, 1931-1939 (Box 21, Folder 298)
    - University of Chicago - Public Administration, 1931-1939 (Box 21, Folder 299)
    - University of Chicago - Public Administration, 1931-1939 (Box 21, Folder 300)
    - University of Chicago - Public Administration, 1940-1944 (Box 22, Folder 301)
    - University of Chicago - Public Administration, 1940-1944 (Box 22, Folder 302)
    - University of Chicago - Public Administration, 1940-1944 (Box 22, Folder 303)
    - University of Chicago - Public Administration, 1940-1944 (Box 22, Folder 304)
    - University of Chicago - Public Administration, 1948-1959 (Box 22, Folder 305)
    - University of Chicago - Public Administration, 1948-1959 (Box 22, Folder 306)
    - University of Chicago - Public Administration - Reports, 1928-1929; 4 items contained in forlder 307-308. (Box 22, Folder 307)
    - University of Chicago - Public Administration - Reports, 1928-1929; 4 items contained in forlder 307-308. (Box 22, Folder 308)
    - University of Chicago - Public Administration - Reports, 1935-1937, 1939; 4 items contained in forlder 309-310. (Box 22, Folder 309)
    - University of Chicago - Public Administration - Reports, 1935-1937, 1939; 4 items contained in forlder 309-310. (Box 22, Folder 310)
    - University of Chicago - Public Services Study, 1948-1950 (Box 22, Folder 311)
    - University of Chicago - Rheinstein, Max - (Refugee, Law), 1934-1939 (Box 22, Folder 312)
    - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration, 1931-1943 (Box 23, Folder 313)
    - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration, 1931-1943 (Box 23, Folder 314)
    - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration, 1931-1943 (Box 23, Folder 315)
    - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration, 1931-1943 (Box 23, Folder 316)
    - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration, 1931-1943 (Box 23, Folder 317)
    - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration, 1931-1943 (Box 23, Folder 318)
    - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration, 1931-1943 (Box 23, Folder 319)
    - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration, 1931-1943 (Box 23, Folder 320)
    - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration, 1931-1943 (Box 23, Folder 321)
    - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration, 1931-1943 (Box 23, Folder 322)
    - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration - Exhibit with Applications, 1931; 8 Items (Box 23, Folder 323)
    - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration - Reports, 1931; 2 Items (Box 23, Folder 324)
    - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration - Reports, 1931-1932; 9 items contained in folders 325-327. (Box 24, Folder 325)
    - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration - Reports, 1931-1932; 9 items contained in folders 325-327. (Box 24, Folder 326)
    - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration - Reports, 1931-1932; 9 items contained in folders 325-327. (Box 24, Folder 327)
    - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration - Reports, 1937-1940; 6 items contained in folders 328-331. (Box 24, Folder 328)
    - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration - Reports, 1937-1940; 6 items contained in folders 328-331. (Box 24, Folder 329)
    - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration - Reports, 1937-1940; 6 items contained in folders 328-331. (Box 24, Folder 330)
    - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration - Reports, 1937-1940; 6 items contained in folders 328-331. (Box 24, Folder 331)
    - University of Chicago - School of Social Service Administration - Pamphlets, 1933-1939; 5 Items (Box 24, Folder 332)
    - University of Chicago - Social Science Documents, 1934-1936 (Box 24, Folder 333)
    - University of Chicago - Social Sciences, 1933-1938 (Box 24, Folder 334)
    - University of Chicago - Social Sciences, 1933-1938 (Box 24, Folder 335)
    - University of Chicago - Social Sciences, 1933-1938 (Box 24, Folder 336)
    - University of Chicago - Social Sciences, 1933-1938 (Box 24, Folder 337)
    - University of Chicago - Social Sciences, 1933-1938 (Box 24, Folder 338)
    - University of Chicago - Social Sciences, 1933-1938 (Box 24, Folder 339)
    - University of Chicago - Social Sciences, 1939-1950 (Box 25, Folder 340)
    - University of Chicago - Social Sciences, 1939-1950 (Box 25, Folder 341)
    - University of Chicago - Social Sciences, 1939-1950 (Box 25, Folder 342)
    - University of Chicago - Social Sciences, 1939-1950 (Box 25, Folder 343)
    - University of Chicago - Social Sciences, 1939-1950 (Box 25, Folder 344)
    - University of Chicago - Social Sciences, 1939-1950 (Box 25, Folder 345)
    - University of Chicago - Social Sciences, 1939-1950 (Box 25, Folder 346)
    - University of Chicago - Social Sciences, 1939-1950 (Box 25, Folder 347)
    - University of Chicago - Social Sciences, 1939-1950 (Box 25, Folder 348)
    - University of Chicago - Social Sciences, 1939-1950 (Box 25, Folder 349)
    - University of Chicago - Social Sciences, 1939-1950 (Box 25, Folder 350)
    - University of Chicago - Social Sciences, 1939-1950 (Box 25, Folder 351)
    - University of Chicago - Social Sciences, 1951-1956 (Box 26, Folder 352)
    - University of Chicago - Social Sciences - Reports, 1931; 2 Items (Box 26, Folder 353)
    - University of Chicago - Social Sciences - Reports, 1939-1941; 3 items contained in folders 354-356. (Box 26, Folder 354)
    - University of Chicago - Social Sciences - Reports, 1939-1941; 3 items contained in folders 354-356. (Box 26, Folder 355)
    - University of Chicago - Social Sciences - Reports, 1939-1941; 3 items contained in folders 354-356. (Box 26, Folder 356)
    - University of Chicago - Social Sciences - Report, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 357)
    - University of Chicago - Social Sciences - Reports, 1948; 6 Items (Box 26, Folder 358)
    - University of Chicago - Social Sciences Faculty, 1931-1937 (Box 26, Folder 359)
    - University of Chicago - Social Sciences Faculty, 1931-1937 (Box 26, Folder 360)
    - University of Chicago - Wagner (Vieira Da Cunba), Mario - (Anthropology), 1943-1946 (Box 26, Folder 361)
    - University of Chicago - War Price Controls, 1941-1945 (Box 27, Folder 362)
    - University of Chicago - War Price Controls, 1941-1945 (Box 27, Folder 363)
    - University of Chicago - War Price Controls, 1941-1945 (Box 27, Folder 364)
    - University of Chicago - War Price Controls, 1941-1945 (Box 27, Folder 365)
    - University of Chicago - War Price Controls, 1941-1945 (Box 27, Folder 366)
    - University of Chicago - War Price Controls, 1941-1945 (Box 27, Folder 367)
    - University of Chicago - War Price Controls, 1941-1945 (Box 27, Folder 368)
    - University of Chicago - War Price Controls - Report, 1943 (Box 27, Folder 369)
    - University of Chicago - War Price Controls - Reprints, 1944-1945; 2 Items (Box 27, Folder 370)
- Indiana, 1928-1935; 217; 1/2 __Box
  Correspondence with the State Board of Health.
  - (Health), 1928-1935 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - (Health), 1928-1935 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Iowa, 1925-1954; 218; 2 Cubic Feet; 4 __Boxes __2 cubic feet
  Grants to Iowa State College and the University of Iowa.
  Five subseries, as follows:
  218 (no program letter, general material which does not fit into a particular program area)
  218 A Medical sciences (research conducted in medical schools or medical applicable to the mental and physical health of human beings)
  218 D Natural sciences and agriculture (research usually conducted in departments outside of medical schools, research in pure science, veterinary medicine or agriculture)
  218 R Humanities and arts
  218 S Social Sciences
  - University of Iowa - Witschi, Emil - (Travel, Zoology), 1948-1950 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - University of Iowa - Witschi, Emil - (Travel, Zoology) - Report, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Iowa - Medical Sciences, 218.A
    - University of Iowa - Brain Physiology - Historical Record, 1925-1927 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - University of Iowa - Medical School - Historical Record, 1922-1949 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - University of Iowa - Barnes, M. E. - (Travel, Preventive Medicine & Public Health), 1935-1936 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Iowa - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 218.D
    - Iowa State College - Fluid Research Fund, 1929-1939 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Iowa State College - Genetics, 1939-1954 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Iowa State College - Genetics, 1939-1954 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Iowa State College - Genetics, 1939-1954 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Iowa State College - Genetics, 1939-1954 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Iowa State College - Genetics, 1939-1954 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Iowa State College - Genetics, 1939-1954 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Iowa State College - Genetics, 1939-1954 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Iowa State College - Genetics - Report, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - University of Iowa - Cell Physiology, 1933-1938 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - University of Iowa - Cell Physiology, 1933-1938 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - University of Iowa - Cell Physiology, 1933-1938 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - University of Iowa - Cell Physiology, 1933-1938 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - University of Iowa - Cell Physiology, 1939-1947 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - University of Iowa - Cell Physiology, 1939-1947 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - University of Iowa - Cell Physiology, 1939-1947 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - University of Iowa - Cell Physiology - Reports, 1936-1939; 3 items contained in folders 22-23. (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - University of Iowa - Cell Physiology - Reports, 1936-1939; 3 items contained in folders 22-23. (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Iowa - Humanities and Arts, 218.R
    - University of Iowa - Drama, 1934-1947 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - University of Iowa - Drama, 1934-1947 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - University of Iowa - Drama, 1934-1947 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - University of Iowa - Drama, 1934-1947 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - University of Iowa - Drama, 1934-1947 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - University of Iowa - Drama, 1934-1947 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - University of Iowa - Drama, 1934-1947 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - University of Iowa - Drama - Reports, 1934; 3 Items (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - University of Iowa - Drama - Reports, 1935-1936; 3 items contained in folders 32-33. (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - University of Iowa - Drama - Reports, 1935-1936; 3 items contained in folders 32-33. (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - University of Iowa - Drama - Supplementary Material, 1936-1944; 3 Items (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - University of Iowa - Radio, 1937-1940 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - University of Iowa - Radio, 1937-1940 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - University of Iowa - Radio - Pamphlets, 1937-1940; 5 Items (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - University of Iowa - Radio - Supplementary Material, 1937-1940; 9 Items (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Iowa - Social Sciences, 218.S
    - Iowa State College - Food Studies, 1942-1945 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Iowa State College - Food Studies, 1942-1945 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Iowa State College - Food Studies, 1942-1945 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Iowa State College - Food Studies, 1942-1945 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Iowa State College - Labor Studies, 1943-1944 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Kansas, 1947-1952; 219; 1/2 __Box
  Correspondence with the Menninger Foundation regarding grants under the medical sciences program.
  219 A Medical sciences (research conducted in medical schools or medical applicable to the mental and physical health of human beings)
  - Kansas - Medical Sciences, 1947-1952; 219.A; 1/2 __Box
    - Menninger Foundation - (Proposed Aid), 1947-1949 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Menninger Foundation - Psychiatric Aides, 1947-1952 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Menninger Foundation - Psychiatric Aides, 1947-1952 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Menninger Foundation - Psychiatric Aides, 1947-1952 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Menninger Foundation - Psychiatric Aides, 1947-1952 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Louisiana, 1928-1949; 221; 4 box(es)
  Grants to Tulane University.
  Three subseries, as follows:
  221 A Medical sciences (research conducted in medical schools or medical applicable to the mental and physical health of human beings)
  221 R Humanities and arts
  221 S Social Sciences
  - Louisiana - Medical Sciences, 221.A
    - Tulane University - Animal Quarters, 1947-1950 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Tulane University - Climatic Factors, 1940-1945 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Tulane University - Climatic Factors, 1940-1945 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Tulane University - Lapham, Maxwell E. - (Travel, Medical School Administration), 1945-1949 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Tulane University - Oberling, Charles - (Refugee, Pathology), 1940-1944 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Tulane University - Oberling, Charles - (Refugee, Pathology), 1940-1944 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Tulane University - Oberling, Charles - (Refugee, Pathology), 1940-1944 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Tulane University - Oberling, Charles - (Refugee, Pathology), 1940-1944 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Tulane University - Perkins, W. H. - (Travel, Public Health), 1935-1937 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Tulane University - Psychiatry, 1936-1945 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Tulane University - Psychiatry, 1936-1945 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Tulane University - Psychiatry, 1936-1945 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Tulane University - Psychiatry, 1936-1945 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Tulane University - Psychiatry - Reports, 1942; 4 Items (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Tulane University - Tropical Medicine, 1928-1944 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Tulane University - Tropical Medicine, 1928-1944 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Tulane University - Tropical Medicine, 1928-1944 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Louisiana - Humanities and Arts, 221.R
    - Tulane University - Library Survey, 1936-1941 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Tulane University - Library Survey, 1936-1941 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Tulane University - Library Survey - Pamphlets, 1937-1939; 4 Items (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Tulane University - Library Survey - Reports, 1937-1939; 8 items contained in folders 21-22. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Tulane University - Library Survey - Reports, 1937-1939; 8 items contained in folders 21-22. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Tulane University - Middle American Research Institute, 1927-1939 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Tulane University - Middle American Research Institute, 1927-1939 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Tulane University - Middle American Research Institute, 1927-1939 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Tulane University - Middle American Research Institute, 1927-1939 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Tulane University - Middle American Research Institute, 1927-1939 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Tulane University - Middle American Research Institute - Reports, 1930-1939; 7 items contained in folders 28-29. (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Tulane University - Middle American Research Institute - Reports, 1930-1939; 7 items contained in folders 28-29. (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Tulane University - Middle American Research Institute - Reprints & Supplementary Material, 1928-1930; 8 Items (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Tulane University - Middle American Research Institute - Reprints & Pamphlets, 1928-1937; 10 Items (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Tulane University - Middle American Research Institute - Museum Catalog, 1938-1941 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Tulane University - Middle American Research Institute - Museum Catalog - Reports, 1939; 3 Items (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Tulane University - Middle American Research Institute - Museum Catalog - Report, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Tulane University - Middle American Research Institute - Museum Catalog - Pamphlets, 1938-1939; 3 Items (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Louisiana - Social Sciences, 221.S
    - Tulane University - School of Social Work, 1932-1945 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Tulane University - School of Social Work, 1932-1945 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Tulane University - School of Social Work, 1932-1945 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Tulane University - School of Social Work, 1932-1945 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Tulane University - School of Social Work, 1932-1945 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Tulane University - School of Social Work - Report, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Tulane University - School of Social Work - Reprints & Pamphlets, 1933; 4 Items (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Maryland, 1929-1939; 223; 1 box(es)
  Public health. Box 1, Folders 1-4 contain International Health Division correspondence with the State Board of Health.
  223 (no program letter, general material which does not fit into a particular program area)
  223 Q Epidemiological investigations and studies
  - (Health), 1929-1939 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - (Health), 1929-1939 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - (Health), 1929-1939 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - (Health) - Report, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Baltimore - Health, 1935-1936 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - KEN-2 Kendrick, J. F. "A Survey of Garret County, Maryland with Special Reference to Health, Medical Care, and Social Welfare", (1936?) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - KEN-5 Kendrick, J. F. "Public Health Administration in Maryland" - Maryland State Planning Commission, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - KEN-6 Kendrick, J. F. "Public Health Administration in Maryland", 1937 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Maryland - Epidemiological Investigations and Studies, 1929-1939; 223.Q; 1 box(es)
    - Anne Arundel County, 1930-1936 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Anne Arundel County, 1930-1936 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Anne Arundel County, 1930-1936 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Anne Arundel County - Reports, 1934-1935; 2 Items (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Dysentery Field Study, 1930-1931 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Dysentery Field Study - Report, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Massachusetts, 1927-1953; 224; 2 Cubic Feet; 5 __Boxes __2 cubic feet
  1930's-1940's mostly grants to the Massachusetts Institute of Technology. International Health Division correspondence with the State Board of Health can be found in Box 5 Folders 52, 54 and 55; and in Box 7 Folders 72-75.
  Eight subseries as follows:
  224 (no program letter, general material which does not fit into a particular program area)
  224 A Medical sciences (research conducted in medical schools or medical research institutes, research directly applicable to the mental and physical health of human beings)
  224 D Natural sciences and agriculture (research usually conducted in departments outside of medical schools, research in pure science, veterinary medicine or agriculture)
  224 K Health services (epidemiology, reform, public health administration, laboratories, vital statistics, and particularly sanitary engineering)
  224 L Public health education (schools of hygiene and public health)
  224 Q Epidemiological investigations and studies 224 R Humanities and arts
  224 T Tuberculosis
  - Anderson, Gaylord W. - (Travel, Public Health), 1931-1932 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Mathematical Biology, 1945-1953 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Mathematical Biology, 1945-1953 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Mathematical Biology, 1945-1953 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Massachusetts - Medical Sciences, 224.A
    - Massachusetts General Hospital - Walter, Grey - (Visit, Electrophysiology), 1946 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Massachusetts - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 224.D
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Aerological Research, 1932-1941 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Aerological Research, 1932-1941 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Aerological Research, 1932-1941 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Aerological Research, 1932-1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Aerological Research - Report, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Bauer, Edmond - (Refugee, Chemistry), 1940-1942 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Bauer, Edmond - (Refugee, Chemistry), 1940-1942 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Biological Engineering, 1937-1940 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Biological Engineering, 1937-1940 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Biological Engineering, 1937-1940 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Biological Engineering, 1937-1940 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Biological Engineering, 1941-1947 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Biological Engineering, 1941-1947 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Biological Engineering, 1941-1947 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Biological Engineering - Application & Supplement, 1938; 2 Items (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Biological Engineering - Pamphlets & Reprints, 1939-1941; 5 Items (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Differential Analyzer, 1932-1950 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Differential Analyzer, 1932-1950 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Differential Analyzer, 1932-1950 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Differential Analyzer, 1932-1950 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Differential Analyzer, 1932-1950 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Differential Analyzer - Reports, 1935-1938, 1945; 7 items contained in folders 27-29. (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Differential Analyzer - Reports, 1935-1938, 1945; 7 items contained in folders 27-29. (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Differential Analyzer - Reports, 1935-1938, 1945; 7 items contained in folders 27-29. (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Differential Analyzer - Reprint, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 30)